

CONTACT ME AT



House No D-48, Street No 02, Gulistan-e-Johar Block 09, Karachi, Pakistan



qaziwaqas144@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/waqas-qazi/



03122278257

SKILLS

•••• MernStack

•••• C/C++

• • • • WordPress

•••• Adobeillustrater/Blender

LANGUAGES

•••• Urdu

••• • English

••• French

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hafiz-e-Quran

WAQAS AHMAD QAZI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT

To achieve a responsible position in a dynamic organization which would enable to utilize all my capabilities and experience and offer a challenging and specifying career with a congenial and working environment and opportunities for learning and growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MernStack Developer

WOL-DP | May 2021 - Present

 Work on Desktop Applications, Andriod/IOS Applications, Websites and more much to resolve the problems in a 6 person team.

Graphic Designer

WOL-DP | May 2021 - Present

 Managed Only our personal software house projects from start to finish.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Ilma University-Formerly IBT

Bachelor's in Software Engineering | Aug 2020- Present

- GPA:3.00
- Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics
- Worked with various startups on launching new Websites and services

Govt.Boys Degree College Karachi

| HSC - Mar 2018-Apr 2020

B.M.B School

SSC- Mar 2016-Apr 2018